### **About Me**

I am Stefanos Michael, a person really passionate with technology and science. I get involved into technology events and I've co-founded Brainstorm. I am a former Microsoft Student Partner and a student member to various tech-related organizations, such as IEEE and StudentGuru Patras. The last two years as a student, I've started to get interested in Robotics, Artificial Intelligence and the Internet of Things, so I started my thesis on "Collection of information & sensor control in a residential environment".

## Languages I speak





English - IGCSE (Grade B)

# **Work Experience**

FreeeWiFi Cyprus July 2017 - present

**Network Engineer** 

iWP & Brand Building July 2017 - present

Web Developer

Brainstorm July 2011 - present

Founder and Developer

Microsoft Student Partner September 2012 - September 2015

**Student Partner** 

National Guard July 2008 - July 2010

**Infantry Sergeant** 



STEFANOS MICHAEL
Electrical & Computer Engineer

Paralimni, Cyprus

17/05/1990

DATE OF BIRTH

15+
PROJECTS
DELIVERED

About Me

Work Experience

Education

Skills

Get in touch:

**▼** stefanos990@outlook.com

stefanos990.com

facebook.com/stefanos990

twitter.com/stefanos990

linkedin.com/in/stefanos990

## **Education**

University of Patras September 2010 - July 2016

**Department** - Electrical & Computer Engineering

Master's equivalent studies (300 ECTS)

**Thesis** - Collection of information and sensor control in a residential environment  $\mathbf{GPA}$  - 7.64 / 10.00

Paralimni Lyceum (High School) September 2005 - June 2008

**GPA - 19.75 / 20.00** 

# **Organizations**

ETEK December 2016 - present

#### Member

The Cyprus Scientific and Technical Chamber (ETEK) is the statutory Technical Advisor to the State and is the umbrella organisation for all Cypriot Engineers. It was established by Law 224/1990 and is a Public Law Body with an elected Governing Body.

IEEE January 2011 - September 2015

#### **Student Member**

IEEE is the world's largest professional association dedicated to advancing technological innovation and excellence for the benefit of humanity. IEEE and its members inspire a global community through IEEE's highly cited publications, conferences, technology standards, and professional and educational activities.

### StudentGuru Patras September 2012 - September 2015

### Member

StudentGuru Patras is the first academic community in University of Patras majoring in Microsoft .NET related technologies. It was founded in October 2009 and its main vision is to bring students closer to popular technologies.

## **Skills and Personal Attributes**





STEFANOS MICHAEL
Electrical & Computer Engineer

Paralimni, Cyprus

17/05/1990

DATE OF BIRTH

15+
PROJECTS
DELIVERED

About Me

Work Experience

Education

Skills

Get in touch:

**■** stefanos990@outlook.com

stefanos990.com

facebook.com/stefanos990

twitter.com/stefanos990linkedin.com/in/stefanos990